me2everyone.com 2009-04-27

# me2everyone.com

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. 

##### **(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a)   information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of        visit and number of page views);

(b)   information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including your name, email address and password);

##### **(2) Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. 

We use “session” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and when you recommend any other person to visit our website (using the referral email system). 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. 

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.)  This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. 

##### (3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a)  Administer the website;

(b)  Enable your use of the services available on the website;

(c)   Send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

(d)  Register shares in me2everyone Limited in your name (subject to the collection of other data including your address which will be done at a later stage;

(e)  Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(f)   Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(g)   Send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by email which you give us permission        to do (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications) and;

(h)  Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing. We will use your personal information purely to assist you during your involvement with me2everyone Limited.

##### **(4) Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you: 

(a)  To the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b)  In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c)   In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d)  To the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling. 

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

##### **(5) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA. 

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

##### (6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure password and firewall protected servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

##### (7) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

##### (8) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email  at any time.  (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

##### (9) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

##### **(10)  Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. There are links in the members area to change your password and email address.

##### (11) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us using the Contact Us link at the bottom of the page or by post to me2everyone Limited, 5 Windmill Close, Bridge, Kent, CT4 5LY, UK. 

##### **(12) Data controller**

The data controller responsible for our website is me2everyone Limited.
